3. Open browser.
9. Navigate to ePulse login page.
15. Enter user name
21. Enter Password
27. Login
31. delay(1)
37. Click the Elections link under Election Setup.
43. Election Creation Step 1 - Choose the file to upload.
49. Election Creation Step 1 - Click Continue once the file is specified.
55. Delay to account for loading times.
59. delay(10)
63. refresh(STOP_ON_FAILURE)
69. Election Creation Step 2 - Enter an election name.
75. Election Creation Step 2 - Enter an election code.
81. Election Creation Step 2 - Select an election type.
85. clearText(findTestObject("Admin Console ePulse Menu/Election Setup/Election Creation/DATE"))
91. Election Creation Step 2 - Select an election date.
97. Election Creation Step 2 - Click Submit to continue to Step 3.
103. Delay to account for load times.
109. Step 3 - Click Done to continue.
115. Delay to account for load times.
121. Step 4 - Click Done to Continue.
127. Delay to account for load times.
133. Step 5 - Click Confirm to finish the setup wizard and create the election.
139. Delay to account for load times.
145. Verify the election created by checking for unique text on the screen.
149. verifyTextPresent("Election Seed Files", true)