3. Open browser.
9. Navigate to ePulse login page.
15. Enter user name
21. Enter Password
27. Login
31. delay(1)
37. Click the Elections link under Election Setup.
43. Election Creation Step 1 - Choose the file to upload.
49. Election Creation Step 1 - Click Continue once the file is specified.
55. Delay to account for loading times.
61. Election Creation Step 2 - Enter an election name.
67. Election Creation Step 2 - Enter an election code.
73. Election Creation Step 2 - Select an election type.
79. Election Creation Step 2 - Select an election date.
85. Delay to account for unpacking times of the uploaded file.
91. Election Creation Step 2 - Click Submit to continue to Step 3.
97. Delay to account for load times.
103. Step 3 - Click Done to continue.